export default { 
  "id": "G10EnglishToSpanish-P2",
  "grade": 10,
  "subject": "Language Arts",
  "title": "Spanish Chapter 4",
  "timeLimit": 30,
  "topic": "grade-10-spanish-11132024-part2",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "conservation",
      "options": ["la conservación", "la contaminación", "el reciclaje"],
      "correctAnswer": "la conservación"
    },
    {
      "question": "pollution",
      "options": ["la contaminación", "la conservación", "la naturaleza"],
      "correctAnswer": "la contaminación"
    },
    {
      "question": "deforestation",
      "options": ["la deforestación", "el reciclaje", "la contaminación"],
      "correctAnswer": "la deforestación"
    },
    {
      "question": "ecology",
      "options": ["la ecología", "la biología", "la geología"],
      "correctAnswer": "la ecología"
    },
    {
      "question": "ecotourism",
      "options": ["el ecoturismo", "el turismo", "la aventura"],
      "correctAnswer": "el ecoturismo"
    },
    {
      "question": "energy",
      "options": ["la energía", "la potencia", "la electricidad"],
      "correctAnswer": "la energía"
    },
    {
      "question": "extinction",
      "options": ["la extinción", "la conservación", "el hábitat"],
      "correctAnswer": "la extinción"
    },
    {
      "question": "government",
      "options": ["el gobierno", "la comunidad", "la sociedad"],
      "correctAnswer": "el gobierno"
    },
    {
      "question": "can",
      "options": ["la lata", "la botella", "la caja"],
      "correctAnswer": "la lata"
    },
    {
      "question": "law",
      "options": ["la ley", "la regla", "la política"],
      "correctAnswer": "la ley"
    },
    {
      "question": "rain",
      "options": ["la lluvia", "la nube", "el agua"],
      "correctAnswer": "la lluvia"
    },
    {
      "question": "danger",
      "options": ["el peligro", "la seguridad", "el riesgo"],
      "correctAnswer": "el peligro"
    },
    {
      "question": "population",
      "options": ["la población", "la comunidad", "el grupo"],
      "correctAnswer": "la población"
    },
    {
      "question": "recycling",
      "options": ["el reciclaje", "la contaminación", "la conservación"],
      "correctAnswer": "el reciclaje"
    },
    {
      "question": "natural resource",
      "options": ["el recurso natural", "la naturaleza", "el material"],
      "correctAnswer": "el recurso natural"
    },
    {
      "question": "solution",
      "options": ["la solución", "el problema", "el resultado"],
      "correctAnswer": "la solución"
    },
    {
      "question": "glass",
      "options": ["el vidrio", "el metal", "el plástico"],
      "correctAnswer": "el vidrio"
    },
    {
      "question": "pure",
      "options": ["puro", "limpio", "natural"],
      "correctAnswer": "puro"
    }
  ]
};
